export const list = [
  {
    question: "What is Peter Parker's Secret Identity?",
    answer: "Spider-Man",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },

  {
    question: "What is Tony Stark's alter ego?",
    answer: "Iron Man",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },

  {
    question: "What is the Incredible Hulk's secret identity",
    answer: "Bruce Banner",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },

  {
    question: "Who is Spider-Man's love interest?",
    answer: "Mary Jane",
    difficulty: "medium",
  },

  {
    question: "What is Wolervine's real name?",
    answer: "Logan",
    difficulty: "medium",
  },

  {
    question: 'Who is the " Merc with a Mouth "?',
    answer: "Deadpool",
    difficulty: "medium",
  },

  {
    question: "Who was the first Ant-Man?",
    answer: "Hank Pym",
    difficulty: "hard",
  },

  {
    question: "Who has a cameo is every Marvel movie?",
    answer: "Stan Lee",
    difficulty: "hard",
  },

  {
    question: "Who is said to be the smartest in the Marvel Universe?",
    answer: "Reed Richards",
    difficulty: "hard",
  },

  {
    question: "What is the name of Thor's Hammer",
    answer: "Mjonir",
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
];
